buyshop4you.com 2018-07-31

# PRIVACY POLICY - BuyShop4You

BuyShop4You.Com is committed to protecting your online privacy. Please read the Privacy Policy carefully to learn what information we collect from you and how we use that information.

By using our website, you acknowledge that you have read, understand, and agree to all the terms of this privacy policy and our website terms of use. If you do not agree to these terms, close the page and do not access or use our website. Should you have any questions about our privacy policy, please email us at support@buyshop4you.com

If we change our privacy policy, we will specify those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement any time, so please review it habitually. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of announcement on our home page.

If you would like to order a product or service we may collect details such as your name, physical address, email address, telephone number, and payment details.

The main purpose as to why we collect this information is to identify and verify your identity to communicate with you about our products or services, as well as obtain payment for your purchase.

We collect information when you engage in certain activities on the Website, such as ordering a product or service from us. When you order products or services, all payments made are completed on secure servers through the likes of Paypal and other payment gateways. Details entered on these sites remains solely between the user and the payment providers, ensuring full security of your sensitive personal information.

Depending on the activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some is identified as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory information for a particular activity that requires it, you will not be permitted to continue with that activity.

We use your information to provide products and services to you, enhance the operation of the Website, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, analyze Website use, and improve our product and service offerings.

In addition, we may store your personal information. We may also use personal details to troubleshoot, resolve disputes, accomplish administrative tasks, contact you, to send promotional offers or newsletters, enforce our agreements with you, including our Website Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy, comply with applicable law, and cooperate with law enforcement activities. You details will never be shared by us to a 3rd party company.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we employ commercially reasonable security measures to protect data and seek to partner with companies, which do the same, we cannot guarantee the security of any information transmitted to or from the Website, and are not responsible for the actions of any third parties that may receive any such information.

To facilitate and customize your experience with the Website, we store cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a User’s computer for record-keeping purposes which contains information about that User. We use cookies to save you time while using the Website, remind us who you are, and track and target User interests in order to provide a customized experience.

This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by our Website only and does not cover the use of cookies by any Advertiser. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may be able to modify your browser settings to decline cookies. Please note that if you decline or delete these cookies, some parts of the Website may not work properly.
